(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
AZKi 7th Birthday Live
Sweet Pop Story
新衣装お披露目＆重大発表あり
AZKi 7th Birthday Live
Sweet Pop Story
New Outfit Reveal & Major Announcement
はっ！おはよう！
Ha! Good morning!
私は今来たところ。全然待ってないよ。
I just got here. I haven't been waiting at all.
むしろ今日は来てくれてありがとう！
Actually, thank you for coming today!
いい天気だね。
It's a nice day, isn't it?
私さ、ずっと君とこうやって公園とか散歩したいと思ってたんだ。
You know, I've always wanted to take a walk in the park like this with you.
あのさ、手、繋いでもいいかな？
Um, is it okay if we hold hands?
やったー！繋いじゃおう！
Yay! Let's hold hands!
手を繋いでるとなんかドキドキするね。
Holding hands makes my heart race a bit.
いよいよこれから生誕ライブか。緊張するな。
My birthday live is finally coming up soon. I'm so nervous.
君ももちろん来てくれるよね？
You're coming too, right?
そうだと思って...
I thought so...
実は今日、君のために手作りのお弁当を作ってきたんだ。
Actually, I made a homemade bento for you today.
一緒に食べよう！
Let's eat together!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
じゃっじゃーん！
Ta-da!
見て！このお弁当箱、可愛いでしょ？
Look! This bento box is cute, isn't it?
中身何入ってると思う？
What do you think is inside?
卵焼き？
Tamagoyaki?
唐揚げ？
Fried chicken?
ハンバーグ？
Hamburg steak?
うーん、なるほど。
Hmm, I see.
正解はこちらでした！
The correct answer was this!
わぁ、美味しそう！
Wow, it looks delicious!
どうかな？あずきの手作りお弁当。
How is it? Azki's homemade bento.
題して「あなたのハートをゼロゲッサー弁当」だよ！
Titled "The ZeroGuesser Bento for Your Heart"!
君の好きな卵焼きもちゃんと入ってます。
Your favorite tamagoyaki is also in there.
正解だよ！
You're right!
それじゃあ何から食べる？
Well then, what will you eat first?
ソーセージ？
Sausage?
トマト？
Tomato?
卵焼き？
Tamagoyaki?
うんうん、やっぱり大好物の卵焼きからか。
Mhm, so it's starting with your favorite tamagoyaki after all.
本当に好きだよね。
You really like it, don't you?
じゃあさ...
Then...
あーんしてあげよっか。
Shall I feed you?
もう、頷きすぎだよ。
Geez, you're nodding too much.
可愛いな。
You're cute.
はい、じゃあ、あーん。
Okay, then, say "ahh".
どう？
How is it?
美味しい？
Is it good?
ありがとう。
Thank you.
嬉しい。
I'm happy.
はい、じゃあもう一口。あーん。
Okay, then another bite. Say "ahh".
美味しそうに食べるね。
You eat with such gusto.
作った甲斐があった！
It was worth making it!
美味しそうに食べてる君も、あずきは好きだよ。
Azki likes you when you're eating happily, too.
食べてる君の姿見てたら、あずきも元気出た。
Watching you eat gave Azki energy, too.
今日の生誕ライブも頑張れそうだよ！
I feel like I can do my best at today's birthday live!
それじゃあ、そろそろリハーサルの時間だから行ってくるね。
Well then, it's almost time for rehearsal, so I'm off.
絶対見つけるからね！
I'll definitely find you!
ライブが終わったらまた待ち合わせね！
Let's meet up again after the live!
せーの！
Ready, go!
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that won't do
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
See, like that
心は進化するよ
My heart will evolve
もっと もっと
More and more
恋愛サーキュレーション / 作詞：meg rock / 作曲：神前 暁 (MONACA)
Ren'ai Circulation / Lyrics: meg rock / Composition: Satoru Kosaki (MONACA)
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If it's a relationship that would vanish if put into words
言葉を消せばいいやって
I thought I should just erase the words
思ってた 恐れてた
I was thinking that, I was afraid
だけど あれ? なんか違うかも..
But wait? Maybe something's different...
せんりのみちもいっぽから!
A journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step!
石のようにかたい そんな意志で
With a will as hard as a rock
ちりもつもればやまとなでしこ?
If dust piles up, it becomes a Yamato Nadeshiko?
「し」抜きで いや 死ぬ気で!
Without the "shi", no, with all my might!
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Softly fluttering, softly floating
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
You call my name
それだけで 宙へ浮かぶ
Just that makes me float into space
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Softly floating, softly fluttering
あなたが笑っている
You are laughing
それだけで 笑顔になる
Just that makes me smile
神様 ありがとう
God, thank you
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが
The fact that we could meet
しあわせなの
Makes me happy
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that won't do
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
See, like that
心は進化するよ
My heart will evolve
もっと もっと
More and more
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yeah, I don't want it like that
ねえ そんなんじゃ まだ
Hey, it's not enough yet
私のこと見ててね
Please keep looking at me
ずっと ずっと
Forever and ever
私の中のあなたほど あなたの中の私の存在は
My existence within you isn't as large as yours within me
まだまだ 大きくないことも わかってるけれど
I know it's not quite that big yet, but
今 この同じ瞬間
Right now, this same moment
共有してる 実感
The feeling of sharing it
ちりもつもればやまとなでしこ!
If dust piles up, it becomes a Yamato Nadeshiko!
略して? ちりつもやまとなでこ!
Abbreviated? Chiri-tsumo Yamato Nadeko!
くららり くららる
Giddily, dizzyingly
あなたを見上げたら
When I look up at you
それだけで まぶしすぎて
Just that is too dazzling
くららる くららり
Dizzyingly, giddily
あなたを想っている
I'm thinking of you
それだけで
Just that alone
とけてしまう
I start to melt
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが
The fact that we met
しあわせなの
Makes me so happy
コイスル キセツハ ヨクバリ circulation
The season of love is a greedy circulation
コイスル キモチハ ヨクバリ circulation
The feeling of love is a greedy circulation
コイスル ヒトミハ ヨクバリ circulation
The eyes of love are a greedy circulation
コイスル オトメハ ヨクバリ circulation
The maiden of love is a greedy circulation
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Floating softly, floating softly
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
When you call my name
それだけで 宙へ浮かぶ
Just that alone makes me float into space
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Floating softly, floating softly
あなたが笑っている
When you're laughing
それだけで 笑顔になる
Just that alone makes me smile
神様 ありがとう
Thank you, God
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's a prank of fate
めぐり逢えたことが
The fact that we met
しあわせなの
Makes me so happy
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's not enough
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
See, it's not enough anymore
心は進化するよ もっともっと
My heart will evolve, more and more
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yeah, I don't like it like that
ねえ そんなんじゃ まだ
Hey, it's still not enough
私のこと 見ててね ずっとずっと
Keep watching me, forever and ever
ひとくち、ちょうだい？
Give me a bite?
作詞・作曲・編曲：渡名航
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: Wataru Tona
ねえ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
恋人みたいなことしてみたいの
I want to try doing things like lovers do
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
ねえ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
……とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...I couldn't say it on today's date
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
I just want one bite
目が合うだけで頬が緩む
My cheeks loosen just by our eyes meeting
目尻のしわくちゃ たまらないの
I can't stand the wrinkles at the corners of your eyes
週末 弾けた恋模様
A love pattern that burst open over the weekend
心が微熱どころではない
My heart is far beyond a slight fever
ときめきの夢に酔いしれて
Drunk on a dream of excitement
いっそこのまま死んでもいい……？！
I might as well die like this...?!
大袈裟じゃないよ 好きだから
It's not an exaggeration, because I love you
時間が止まってしまったらいいのにな
I wish time would just stop
幸せを噛みしめていたいな
I want to savor this happiness
ずっとこのまま 覚めないで
Stay like this forever, don't wake up
あともう一口だけ
Just one more bite
許されるならば夢を見せて
If it's allowed, let me dream
ねえ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
間接キスなんてもう気にしないよ
I don't care about indirect kisses anymore
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
ねえ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
……あなたが好きすぎて言い出せないよ
...I love you too much to say it
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
I just want one bite
もうそろそろ気持ちが爆発しそうだよ
My feelings are about to explode soon
抱きしめてみたいよ
I want to try hugging you
でも引かれたら立ち直れないし…… 臆病なの、変わらないや
But if you're repulsed, I won't recover... I'm a coward, that hasn't changed
目が合うだけで心臓が跳ぶ
My heart jumps just by our eyes meeting
せめて手だけは繋ぎたいの
I want to at least hold hands
週末 弾けた恋模様
A love pattern that burst open over the weekend
心が微熱どころではない
My heart is far beyond a slight fever
もう一度 夢に酔いしれて
Drunk on a dream once more
連れ出して！
Take me away!
いっそこのまま死んでもいい……？！
I might as well die like this...?!
大袈裟じゃないよ 好きだから
It's not an exaggeration, because I love you
時間が止まってしまったらいいのにな
I wish time would just stop
幸せを噛みしめていたいな
I want to savor this happiness
ずっとこのまま 覚めないで
Stay like this forever, don't wake up
あともう一口だけ
Just one more bite
許されるならば夢を見せて
If it's allowed, let me dream
日が暮れるまで傍に居て
Stay by my side until the sun sets
初キスはもう少し後で
Save our first kiss for a little later
束縛は強めでOK？
Is it okay if I'm a bit clingy?
受け止めて 受け止めて
Accept it, accept it
何も言わずに手を引いて
Take my hand without saying anything
そのまま遠くへ連れてって
And take me far away just like that
どこまでも どこまでも
Anywhere, anywhere
ねえ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that
一口だけ食べたいの
I only want to eat one bite
……とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...I couldn't say it on today's date
......とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...I couldn't say it during today's date.
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
I just want to take a bite.
今、私は恋してるの！
Now, I am in love!
はい！ということで、みんな！
Alright! So, everyone!
こんこんこんこんこんあずきー！
Kon-kon-kon-kon-kon, AZKi!
右手にマイク、左手に地図
Mic in my right hand, map in my left hand,
あなたのハート、ゼロゲッサー！
the Zero-Guesser of your heart!
AZKiでーす！
I'm AZKi!
ということで、えー、本日は
So, um, today,
AZKi 7th Birthday Live 「Sweet Pop Story」にお越しくださり
thank you so much for coming to AZKi 7th Birthday Live
ありがとうございます！
"Sweet Pop Story"!
わーい、わーい、わーい！始まった始まった！
Yay, yay, yay! It's started, it's started!
えー、なんと活動を始めて7回目の
Um, somehow, I've reached my 7th
誕生日を迎えることができました！
birthday since I started my activities!
本当に本当に、いつも応援してくれる開拓者の皆のおかげで
Really, really, it's all thanks to the Pioneers who support me
今日の日が、この日があると思っています。
that this day exists. I truly believe that.
いつもありがとう！
Thank you as always!
ということで、なんとね、もう今日は
So, surprisingly, today,
冒頭からじゃじゃーん！
right from the start, ta-da!
新衣装お披露目でございます！
it's time for the reveal of my new outfit!
どうかな？どうかな？
How is it? How is it?
どう？どう？どう？どう？どう？
What do you think? What do you think?
はい、今回の新衣装のテーマはですね
Yes, the theme of this new outfit is...
ゆるふわ私服衣装となっております！
...a soft and fluffy casual outfit!
可愛いでしょ？可愛いでしょ？
It's cute, right? It's cute, right?
ということでね、こういう私服っぽくて可愛い衣装がいいな、欲しいなって思っていたので
I've been thinking I'd like a cute, casual outfit like this,
今回お仕立てしていただきました！
so I had it tailored for this occasion!
そしてね、今日のこのライブステージも、この衣装に合わせて
And today's live stage is also designed to match this outfit.
なんと、なんと、見てください皆さん！
Look, everyone!
ちょっとお部屋っぽく、ちょっと何か
It's a bit room-like, and looks like a place
デートもできそうなステージになっております！
where you could go on a date!
ね、この新衣装にぴったりのステージになってます！
It's a stage that perfectly fits this new outfit!
はい！ということで今日はね、あのこの配信のハッシュタグ！
Alright! So today, the hashtag for this stream is...
右上、こっち！これ、これ、これ、これ！
...up there on the right! This one, this one!
#AZKi生誕ライブ2025 でたくさんたくさんポストしてください！
#AZKi生誕ライブ2025. Please post a lot with it!
スクショとか感想とか、全部全部AZKiもチェックしますんで
I'll be checking all the screenshots and comments,
可愛いAZKiをスクショするんだ、よろしくね！
so take lots of screenshots of cute AZKi, okay?
お願いしまーす！
Please!
え、そしてそして、今日はですね、新衣装のお披露目だけでなく
And today isn't just about the new outfit reveal,
重大発表もありますので、ぜひ最後まで見てください！
there are also major announcements, so please watch until the end!
よろしくね！
I'm counting on you!
はい！ということでね、早速ライブが始まったわけなんですが
Alright! So, the live has just started,
ま、ちょっと今回は「Sweet Pop Story」ということで
but since the title is "Sweet Pop Story,"
物語風に、ちょっとデートなんかしてみちゃったり、はい
I'm making it like a story, with a bit of a date theme.
してね、今日のライブ楽しんでいただけたらなと思います！
I hope you enjoy today's live with that in mind!
で、1曲目は「恋愛サーキュレーション」、そして2曲目は「ヒトクチチョウダイ」というね
The first song was "Renai Circulation," and the second was "Hitokuchi Choudai."
オリジナル曲でございました！
They're original songs!
どうだったかな？可愛かった？
How was it? Was it cute?
ということで、ここから、なんとみんなお待ちかねのゲストブロックになります！
Now, from here, it's the guest block you've all been waiting for!
大好きなあのメンバーと可愛い曲を歌っちゃいますので
I'll be singing cute songs with members I love,
ぜひぜひ楽しんでいただけたらと思います！
so please enjoy it!
それじゃあ行くよ！どうぞ！
Here we go! Enjoy!
心予報
Kokoro Yohou
作詞・作曲：Eve
Lyrics & Composition: Eve
薄つく甘い街の喧騒
The faintly sweet bustle of the city
ゆえに感情線は渋滞
Because of that, the heart lines are congested
「僕に関係ない」とか言って
Saying things like "It has nothing to do with me"
心模様　白く染まって
The heart's pattern is dyed white
だけどどうやったって釣り合わない
But no matter what, they don't match
いたずらに笑う横顔に乾杯
A toast to that mischievously smiling profile
酸いも甘いも分からないの
I don't know the sour or the sweet
きっと君の前では迷子
I'm surely a lost child in front of you
溶かしてはランデブー
Melting away in a rendezvous
プラトニックになってく
Becoming platonic
ほろ苦い期待　張り裂けてしまいそう
Bittersweet expectations, about to burst
だから
Therefore
夢惑う
Being lost in a dream
想いならば
If it's feelings...
聞かせて
...let me hear...
その声を
...that voice.
君に染まってしまえば 染まってしまえば
If I'm dyed in your color, if I'm dyed in your color...
心遊ばせ 余所見しないで
Let your heart play, don't look away...
想っていたいな 想っていたいな
I want to keep thinking of you, I want to keep thinking of you...
桃色の心予報
A pink heart forecast.
今 混ざってしまえば 混ざってしまえば
If we mix now, if we mix...
君と重なって 視線が愛 相まって
Overlapping with you, our gazes and love intermingling...
ロマンスは止まらない
Romance won't stop.
失敗したらグッバイステップ
If I fail, it's a goodbye step.
神さま どうか今日は味方して
God, please be on my side today.
おかしな君は笑って
Strange you, you laugh.
逆さま世界が顔出して
An upside-down world shows its face.
夢ならまだ覚めないで
If it's a dream, please don't wake up yet.
心模様 赤に染まってく
The pattern of my heart is turning red.
冷静沈着では どう頑張ったって居られない
No matter how hard I try, I can't stay calm and collected.
大体 視界に居ない
You're mostly not in my sight.
ちょっとlateなスターライトナイト
A slightly late starlight night.
最低な昨日にさえ さよなら言いたいような
I feel like saying goodbye even to the worst yesterday.
甘いおまじないかけられてしまいそう
I feel like I'm about to have a sweet spell cast on me.
だから
So,
この夜を越えてゆけ
...go beyond this night.
響かせて
Let it resonate,
その想いを
...those feelings.
君に染まってしまえば...
If I'm dyed in your color...
君だけ想っていたいな
I want to keep thinking only of you.
君に染まってしまえば 染まってしまえば
If I'm dyed in your color, if I'm dyed in your color...
心遊ばせ 余所見しないで
Let your heart play, don't look away...
想っていたいな 想っていたいな
I want to keep thinking of you, I want to keep thinking of you...
桃色の心予報
A pink heart forecast.
今 伝えてしまえ 伝えてしまえば
Now, just tell you, if I tell you...
君と重なって 視線が愛 相まって
Overlapping with you, our gazes and love intermingling...
失敗したらグッバイステップ
If I fail, it's a goodbye step.
神さま どうか今日は味方して
God, please be on my side today.
「スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！」
"Fall in love! You absolutely must fall in love!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
A magic spell, decorating everything including you.
朝からビターなキモチ
A bitter feeling since morning.
だって知らない表情（かお）で笑った
Because you laughed with a face I didn't know.
ちょっと髪に触れたりしちゃって
Touched your hair a little bit...
なんでハナの下伸ばしてんの！？
Why are you making such a silly face!?
どんどん膨れていくジェラシー
Jealousy keeps growing...
スフレみたいに甘くないよ
It's not sweet like a soufflé.
胸いっぱいに溢れちゃって
Overflowing in my chest...
ダメダメ！気付かれちゃうよ！
No, no! You'll notice!
バレないように…でも気付いて！フクザツな乙女心
So you don't find out... but please notice! A complicated maiden's heart.
「スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！」
"Fall in love! You absolutely must fall in love!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
A magic spell, decorating everything including you.
恋心ちょっとキャラメリゼ
A little bit of caramelized love.
焦がしたらずっとスキにさせるから！
If I char it, I'll make you love me forever!
今日は朝からちょっとラッキー
A bit lucky since this morning.
あくびこらえた変顔見ちゃった
Saw your funny face while holding back a yawn.
肩叩きながら「おはよう」なんて言えたらもっと…ああもうイケナイ！
If only I could say "Good morning" while tapping your shoulder... Oh, I can't do that!
ふぅ…ちょっと落ち着いて？
Phew... calm down a bit?
悶えすぎて零れちゃうよ
Writhing too much, it's gonna spill out.
「なにしてんの？」ってほっぺツンツン
"What are you doing?" poking your cheek.
いきなりまさかの不意打ち禁止～！
No sudden surprise attacks allowed!
メレンゲハート 耳までチュイール
Meringue heart, tuile up to the ears.
アツいのは私だけ？
Am I the only one who's hot?
スキすぎる！あぁ…スキすぎる！
I love you too much! Ah... I love you too much!
ココロから スペシャリテのアイラヴユー
From the bottom of my heart, a specialité "I love you".
恋心もっとナブラージュ
Love, even more nappage.
溶けたならハート型にグラッセせよ
If it melts, glaze it into a heart shape.
アナタにだけ 教えてあげる
I'll tell only you...
このキモチのヒミツ
...the secret of this feeling.
「ダイスキだよ」
"I love you."
「スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！」
"Fall in love! You absolutely must fall in love!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
A magic spell, decorating everything including you.
A spell, decorating you all over
このキモチ ずっとアラカルト
These feelings, always a la carte
おすそわけ ココロごとデコレーション
Sharing, decorating my heart and all
恋心 いっぱいプレゼント
A present full of love
届いたら 私ごと召し上がれ♪
If it reaches you, please have me along with it♪
Lalala...♪
ほめのび / 作詞・作曲：渡辺翔 / 編曲：倉内達矢
Homenobi / Lyrics & Composition: Sho Watanabe / Arrangement: Tatsuya Kurauchi
なーにしよっか練習中
In the middle of practicing what to do
しれっとこそっと準備進行
Preparing quietly and sneakily
心境 緊張 で焦る
Feeling nervous and in a panic
言わんけどつよつよアリでしょ？
I won't say it, but being strong is okay, right?
元気配るから待っててって
I'll share some energy, so wait for me
そうやって成長する子です
That's how I grow
いいかな？
Is it okay?
ゆるポンでOK？
Is 'Yuru Pon' OK?
いちにーさん
One, two, three
テンパっちゃってOK？
Is it OK if I panic?
始めちゃおう
Let's get started
ほめてほしいな ほめてほしいな
I want to be praised, I want to be praised
ほめてくれたら2割増しでがんばる
If you praise me, I'll work 20% harder
見ててほしいな 見ててほしいな
I want you to watch me, I want you to watch me
ほめちぎられて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type that grows when showered with praise
もーお
Geez
なぁーんにも出てこない
Nothing's coming to me
頭ん中真っ白だ
My head is a complete blank
さっぱりだ うんうん あれ？
Nothing at all, yeah yeah, huh?
まっいっか
Well, whatever
でこぼこな情緒 提供中
Offering up bumpy emotions
ぽかんとして何しちょんの
Staring blankly, what are you doing?
こんなんが通常のわたし
This is how I usually am
いいでしょ
It's fine, right?
それではOK？
Is it OK then?
いちにーさん
One, two, three
落ち着きOK？
Are you calm?
始めちゃおう
Let's get started
どうしたらいいの？どうしたらいいの？
What should I do? What should I do?
どうすればみんなハッピーで笑顔バッチリ
What can I do to make everyone happy and smiling perfectly
こちらへどうぞ こちらへどうぞ
This way, please; this way, please
押さず慌てず並んで合図です
Don't push, don't rush, line up for the signal
もーお
Geez
聞こえてる？
Can you hear me?
にゃんにゃんにゃん
Nyan nyan nyan
楽しんでる？
Are you having fun?
ポンポンポン
Pon pon pon
こっちだよ
Over here
ほめてほしいな ほめてほしいな
I want to be praised, I want to be praised
ほめてくれたら2割増しでがんばる
If you praise me, I'll work 20% harder
見ててほしいな 見ててほしいな
I want you to watch me, I want you to watch me
ほめちぎられて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type that grows when showered with praise
まーたね
See you again
sweet night, sweet time... / 作詞・作曲・編曲：佐藤厚平(Hifumi,inc.)
sweet night, sweet time... / Lyrics, Composition & Arrangement: Kohei Sato (Hifumi,inc.)
sweet night, sweet time...
そっと日の沈む 茜色の空
The sun sets softly in the madder-red sky
やっと目覚めた きみに挨拶
Finally awake, I greet you
えっと明日は 休みだから
Um, since tomorrow is a holiday
一晩中きみといっしょに
I'll be with you all night long
sweet night, sweet time...
眠くないよ 眠くないの
I'm not sleepy, I'm not sleepy.
sweet night, sweet time...
まだまだ遊びたい
I still want to play more.
sweet night, sweet time...
話したいよ 話し足んないの
I want to talk, I haven't talked enough.
夢の中じゃ物足りないから
Because it's not enough in my dreams.
今夜は 眠れ眠らない
Tonight, sleep... don't sleep,
きみとリズム合わせ
syncing rhythms with you.
昼夜逆転を楽しむの
I'm enjoying day and night reversal.
今だけ 眠れ眠らない
Just for now, sleep... don't sleep,
星空散歩して
walking in the starry sky.
夜がどうか 明けないように
May the night somehow not end.
いつまでも sweet night, sweet time...
Forever, sweet night, sweet time...
きっと話すのも笑うのも
Surely talking and laughing too,
もっと誰かと繋がるために
to connect more with someone.
ちょっと俯いたきみへ向けて
Towards you, who looked down a little,
一晩中 歌ってもいい
it's okay to sing all night long.
sweet night, sweet time... 眠らないよ 眠らないの
sweet night, sweet time... I won't sleep, I won't sleep.
sweet night, sweet time... 夜ごと遊びたい
sweet night, sweet time... I want to play every night.
sweet night, sweet time... 喋りたいよ 喋り足んないの
sweet night, sweet time... I want to talk, I haven't talked enough.
sweet night, sweet time... きみと朝まで
sweet night, sweet time... with you until morning.
月も知らない
Even the moon doesn't know.
ナイショ話を
A secret talk...
パジャマのままで
still in our pajamas.
お願い 夢の中じゃ物足りないから
Please, because it's not enough in my dreams.
もう少し 眠れ眠らない
A little more, sleep... don't sleep,
きみとリズム合わせ
syncing rhythms with you.
昼夜逆転を楽しむの
I'm enjoying day and night reversal.
今だけ 眠れ眠らない
Just for now, sleep... don't sleep,
白昼夢見送って
sending off the daydream.
夜を越えよう
Let's get through the night.
また明日もここで会おう
Let's meet here again tomorrow.
good night, good time... また明日
good night, good time... see you tomorrow.
good night, good time...
というわけで ゲストブロックお送りしました！
And so, that was the guest block!
どうだったかな？ どうだったかな？
How was it? How was it?
はい。ということでゲストパートなんですが、ここまでを振り返ると
Yes. So, for the guest part, looking back on what we've seen so far...
いろはちゃんと『心予報』お届けしました！
I performed "Kokoro Yoho" with Iroha-chan!
なんとね、いろはちゃんのあの新衣装3Dでね、一緒にこれはあずいろてぇてぇ
Amazingly, with Iroha-chan in that new 3D outfit, we did some "AzuIro te-te" together.
あずいろてぇてぇをしたいと思って
I really wanted to experience some "AzuIro te-te",
一緒にね、歌ってみたを出した『心予報』をちょっと踊って
so we danced a bit to "Kokoro Yoho," which we'd released a cover of together,
一緒にこの新衣装であずいろてぇてぇしました。
and showed off our "AzuIro te-te" in this new outfit.
どうだった？ どうだった？ 良かったでしょう？
How was it? How was it? It was good, right?
そして、次はラミィちゃんと『初恋パティシエール』という
And next, with Lamy-chan, we sang "Hatsukoi Patissiere",
ラミィちゃんのオリ曲をね、もうこのライブのテーマに絶対合うと思って
Lamy-chan's original song, which I thought would definitely fit the theme of this live,
一緒に歌わせていただきました。
together.
可愛かった！
It was so cute!
そしてそして、団長と『ホメノビ』！
And then, with Danchou, "Homenobi"!
これはね、ずっとずっとあずき一緒に団長とホメノビを歌うのが夢だったんで
Singing "Homenobi" with Danchou has been a dream of mine for a long, long time,
もうこのライブで実現するぞと思って
so I decided to make it happen at this live,
ホメノビで成長していきたいと甘えました。
and I indulged myself, wanting to grow through "Homenobi".
そしてそして、わためと一緒に、わためのオリジナル曲
And then, with Watame, we sang Watame's original song,
『Sweet Night, Sweet Time』を歌わせていただきました。
"Sweet Night, Sweet Time" together.
もうこれもね、今回のコンセプトにめちゃくちゃ合う、わためとこの曲一緒に歌いたいなって思って選曲しました。
This song also fits perfectly with this time's concept, and I chose it because I really wanted to sing it with Watame.
どうだったかなー？
How was it?
いや、嬉しいね、ホロメンのオリ曲歌ったりできるの、本当にライブならではという感じで
Man, I'm so happy. Being able to sing Holomem original songs really feels like a special live concert experience.
お送りしましたが...
We presented those, but...
まだまだゲストパート続きますんで
the guest part still continues.
セトリストのあずきさんにもご注目ください！
Please also keep an eye on setlist-AZKi!
ということで、まだまだゲストパートいくぞ！
So, here we go, more guest parts!
尻尾ふってスカウト
Tail-wagging scout
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering more cute girls
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
If we gather together, we'll be the strongest!
かわいにちっく！
作詞・編曲：HoneyWorks, MARUMOCHI
伴奏：HoneyWorks
Kawaii Nichikku!
Lyrics/Arrangement: HoneyWorks, MARUMOCHI
Accompaniment: HoneyWorks
文化祭が始まる
The school festival is starting
最大規模でいきたいの
I want to go all out on the largest scale
君も参加してよね
You should participate too
ねえチケット無制限
Hey, the tickets are unlimited
校長先生もビックリ
Even the principal will be surprised
キャスト足んない 大焦り
Not enough cast members, we're panicking
ワンワン泣いちゃう うう うう
I'll cry out loud, woof woof
本番間近はキリキリ
Things get hectic as the show approaches
運営の予算はギリギリ
The management's budget is paper-thin
すねちゃうぞ
I'm gonna sulk
泣いちゃうぞ
I'm gonna cry
テレフォンナンバー
pi pi pi pi pi
Telephone number
「イケてる子を用意して」
"Get me someone cool"
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello? I'm the organizer
可愛い子 チェック！スカウター！
Check the cute girls! Scouter!
超超超！超絶調！美少女ゲットだぜっ☆
Super super super! In top form! Caught a beautiful girl☆
美少女(こ)捕まえだ☆
I've caught a beautiful girl☆
もしも私が死んだなら
If I were to die one day
バーチャル葬でド派手にねっ
Give me a flashy virtual funeral
それくらい本気でやりたいの
That's how serious I want to be about this
尻尾ふってスカウト
Tail-wagging scout
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering more cute girls
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
If we gather together, we'll be the strongest!
あー無駄三昧しんどいわ
Ah, indulging in wastefulness is exhausting
どうしようもない焦燥感
A sense of helplessness and impatience
タイムリミットはあとちょっと！？
The time limit is almost up!?
ここでもういっちょ！
Here's one more!
美味しいころね食べたら
If you eat a delicious Korone
犬に金棒 最強よ
It's like an ogre with a club, the strongest
東西南北 駆け回り
Running around North, South, East, and West
まだ見ぬあの子 探し出せ！
Find that girl we haven't seen yet!
ワンワン泣いちゃう わおん
Woof woof crying out loud, waon
呼んだらどこでも駆けつけます！
I'll rush anywhere if you call!
いい子がいたら 教えてね
If there's a good kid, let me know
噛んじゃうぞ
I'll bite you
甘えちゃうぞ
I'll spoil you
テレフォンナンバー
pi pi pi pi pi
Telephone number
「イケてる子が見つかった？」
"Did you find someone cool?"
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello? I'm the organizer
可愛い子 チェック！スカウター！
Check the cute girls! Scouter!
超超超！超絶調！美少女ゲットだぜっ☆
Super super super! In top form! Caught a beautiful girl☆
美少女(こ)捕まえだ☆
I've caught a beautiful girl☆
もしも私が死んだなら
If I were to die one day
バーチャル葬でド派手にねっ
Give me a flashy virtual funeral
それくらい本気でやりたいの
That's how serious I want to be about this
尻尾ふってスカウト
Tail-wagging scout
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering more cute girls
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
If we gather together, we'll be the strongest!
自薦他薦は問いません
Self-recommendations or others are all welcome
「私、君を待ってるよ」
"I'm waiting for you"
うー あー もー はい
Uu... Aa... Moo... Yes!
やだやだミスってらんない、ね？
No way, I can't afford to mess up, right?
ベイビーダンス
作詞・作曲：DECO*27
編曲：Rockwell
Baby Dance
Lyrics/Composition: DECO*27
Arrangement: Rockwell
真っ赤なハート差し出して...
Presenting a bright red heart...
そんなのやっぱ妄想じゃん
That's just a delusion after all
そっちはどう思ってるの？
What are you thinking over there?
言いかけてしまう無理みたい
I'm about to say it, but I can't
こんなんじゃーってわかってるんだ
I know it shouldn't be like this
思うほどにはまっていくんだ
I'm falling for it more than I realize
頑張りたいあたしに期待
I hope for myself to do my best
ぎゅーだってしたいかも... かもん
I might even want to hug... come on
ちょっとは変われていますか？
Have I changed even a little bit?
足りないとこばっかだけど
Even though I have so many flaws
ポンでコツでドジじゃないあたしだったら
If I weren't clumsy and such a mess
きみはだめだよね？
You wouldn't like that, right?
ねぇもうやだやだミスってらんない
Hey, I can't afford to mess up anymore
もうやだやだ踊ってベイビーダンス
No more, no more, dance the baby dance
あたしはまだ諦めない
I'm not giving up just yet
でもでも 全然だめかも
But still, it might be no good at all
だってベイビーダンス うまくできないの
Because it's a baby dance, I can't do it well
だってベイビーダンス 伝えられないの
Because it's a baby dance, I can't convey it
もっと可愛くなりたいのに
Even though I want to become cuter
どうしたらいいかわかんないし
I just don't know what to do
やだやだミスってらんない、ね？
No way, I can't afford to mess up, right?
あ〜やっちまった こんなはずじゃ
Ah~ I messed up, it wasn't meant to be like this
どうしてどうして わかっているのに
Why, why, even though I know better
見たくないとこ透けちゃって
The parts I don't want to see are showing through
無理無理 でも期待はしたいの いいですか？
It's impossible, but I still want to hope, okay?
ポンもコツもドジも全部あたしなんだよ
All the clumsiness and messiness, that's just who I am
ちゃんと見ていてほしい
I want you to look at me properly
ねぇもうやだやだぐずって後悔
Hey, I can't stand sulking and regretting anymore
もうやだやだ回ってベイビーダンス
No more, no more, spinning baby dance
だめなあたし塗り替えたい
I want to repaint my useless self
でもでも 全然だめかも
But still, it might be no good at all
だってベイビーダンス うまくできないな
Because it's a baby dance, I just can't do it well
だってベイビーダンス 伝えられないの
Because it's a baby dance, I can't convey it
もっと可愛くなりたいのに
Even though I want to become cuter
どうしたらいいかわかんないし
I just don't know what to do
まだまだいけるかな
I wonder if I can still keep going
まだまだ
Still, still,
言えるかな
can I say it?
まだまだ
Still, still,
できるかな
can I do it?
まだまだ…うぅ…
Still, still... ugh...
ポンコツでドジでだめで足りないとこばっかだって
Useless, clumsy, and full of flaws...
きっとやめないんだ
But I surely won't stop.
ポンコツでドジでだめで足りないとこばっかだって
Useless, clumsy, and full of flaws...
見ていてほしい
I want you to watch me.
ういぇー！
Woo-yeah!
ねえもうやだやだミスってらんない
Hey, I've had enough, I can't keep making mistakes.
もうやだやだ踊ってベイビーダンス
I've had enough, dance the Baby Dance.
あたしはまだ諦めない
I won't give up yet.
ほらほら全然だめじゃない
Look, it's not a total failure, is it?
だってベイビーダンス
Because it's the Baby Dance,
うまくできるから
because I'll be able to do it well.
だってベイビーダンス
Because it's the Baby Dance,
伝えられるから
because I can convey it.
もっと可愛くなりたいから
Because I want to become cuter,
どんな時だってそう頑張れるし
no matter when, I can work hard like that.
だってベイビーダンス
Because it's the Baby Dance,
きみに届くまで
until it reaches you.
だってベイビーダンス
Because it's the Baby Dance,
きみに会えるまで
until I can meet you.
もっと可愛くなりたいから
Because I want to become cuter,
どんな時だってそう頑張れるし
no matter when, I can work hard like that.
やだやだミスってらんないね？
I've had enough, can't keep making mistakes, right?
Smile!
Sweet!
Sister!
Sadistic!
Surprise!
Service!
We are STEELE!!
さあ扉を開けて
Now open the door
未知なるパラダイス
An unknown paradise
体験しよう
Let's experience it
おいで
Come on over
そうキミを待つのは
Yes, waiting for you is
不思議なオアシス
A mysterious oasis
ほっこり日常に
In your warm daily life
ちょっぴりSpice
A little bit of spice
ぐるんぐるんかきまぜちゃうんだ
Spinning, spinning, I'll mix it all up
ぐるんぐるん当店自慢のフレーバー
Spinning, spinning, our shop's proud flavor
サービスサービスご褒美タイム
Service service, reward time
おもてなしココロこめて
Hospitality with all my heart
Welcome to...
わたしたちと一緒に
Together with us
めくるめくワンダーデイドリーム
A dazzling wonder daydream
愛情マシマシ煩悩なでなで
Extra affection, worldly desires headpats
誠心誠意つとめます
We'll serve you with all our heart and soul
イエス！
Yes!
キミの元気チャージに
To recharge your energy
ひと役買えるかな
I wonder if I can play a part
こーいった感じも
This kind of feeling
あーいった感じも
And that kind of feeling
意外と悪くないでしょ？
They're not too bad, right?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend
キミにきゅんきゅんきゅん
Making your heart go kyun kyun kyun
ハートにぱんちぱんちぱんち
Punch punch punch to your heart
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend
お口に合いますか？
Is it to your liking?
お口に合うといいな♪
I hope it's to your liking♪
ぱなぺてぃーと
Bon Appétit
ぱなぺてぃー？
Bon Appétit?
ぱなぺてぃー！
Bon Appétit!
千客万来！
A full house!
ちょっと、なんか不本意ながらも
Wait, somewhat against my will
いつだって需要は斜め上
Demand is always coming from out of left field
そんじゃいっか、ホントのわたしは
Well that's okay, the real me
シークレットモードで営業スイッチオン
Is in secret mode, business switch on
ぐるんぐるん言わせてもっと
Spinning, spinning, make them say more
ぐるんぐるんキミ仕様のフレイバー
Spinning, spinning, a flavor tailored to you
サービスサービス極上タイム
Service service, superb time
癒しとはかくあるべき
Healing should be just like this
Welcome to...
わたしたちのお店に
To our shop
本日もようこそ
Welcome again today
おかえり待ってたリピート嬉しいな
Welcome back, I was waiting, I'm happy for the repeat
店員一同歓迎
The whole staff welcomes you
イエス！
Yes!
キミのお疲れさまに
For your hard work
ピッタリのレシピで
With the perfect recipe
こーゆうのどうかな
How about this?
あーゆうのアリかな
Is that okay?
よろこんでもらえてるかな
I wonder if you're enjoying it
Smile!
Sweet!
Sister!
Sadistic!
More!
Strange!
Serious!
Selfish!
Surprise!
Secret!
Super!
We are STEELE!!
さあ扉を開けて
Now open the door
愉快なパラダイス
A pleasant paradise
怖がらずにおいで
Don't be afraid, come on in
そう、いつも通りの毎日に
Yes, to your usual daily life
イロドリと
With color
アソビゴコロ
And playfulness
召し上がれ
Please enjoy
ブレンド・S
Blend S
Welcome to...
わたしたちと一緒に
Together with us
めくるめくワンダーデイドリーム
A dazzling wonder daydream
愛情マシマシ煩悩なでなで
Extra affection, worldly desires headpats
誠心誠意つとめます
We'll serve you with all our heart and soul
いえーす！
Yes!
キミの元気チャージに
To recharge your energy
ひと役買えるかな
I wonder if I can play a part
こーいった感じも
This kind of feeling
あーいった感じも
And that kind of feeling
意外と悪くないでしょ？
They're not too bad, right?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono Buono, I want to blend
キミにきゅんきゅんきゅん
Kyun kyun kyun for you
ぱんちぱんちぱんち
Punch punch punch
Buono Buono
ブレンドしたい
I want to blend
お口にあいますか？
Does it suit your palate?
お好み聞かせてね
Let me hear your preferences
お口にあうといいな
I hope it suits your palate
というわけで、引き続きゲストブロックをお送りしました！
And so, we've just presented the guest block!
どうだったかな？ どうだったかな？
How was it? How was it?
はい、ということで、この後はですね、重大発表もございますので、ぜひ最後まで見ててねー！
Yes, so after this, there's a major announcement, so please watch until the end!
はい、そんなゲストブロックの後半なんですが、ころさんと可愛い子チェックでしっぽふりふりしました！
Yes, in the second half of that guest block, I wagged tails with Korone-san for the 'cute girl check'!
そして、みこちとベビーダンスをお送りしましたね。
And then we performed the 'Baby Dance' with Miko-chi.
一緒になんか私服衣装でね、シナジーあったんじゃないかなって思います。
With the matching casual outfits, I think we had some great synergy.
そしてそして、ふわもこちゃんと『ぼなぺてぃーと♡S』をお届けしました！
And then, we performed "Bon Appétit ♡ S" with Fuwamoco-chan!
いや、ふわもこちゃんとね、一緒にこうやって3Dライブしたいなと思ってたので、
I've always wanted to do a 3D live together with Fuwamoco-chan, so...
もう念願念願かなって、AZKiのやりたいことを全部全部詰め込んだゲストパートでございました！
it was a long-held wish come true. This guest part was packed with everything AZKi wanted to do!
はい、ということで、重大発表もあるんですけど、その前に、皆さん、あのお知らせがございます！
Yes, so there's a major announcement coming up, but before that, everyone, I have an announcement!
AZKi誕生日記念2025グッズ販売告知！こちらをご覧ください！
Announcement of AZKi Birthday Celebration 2025 merchandise! Please take a look at this!
AZKi 誕生日記念 2025
AZKi Birthday Celebration 2025
うおー！ 今回もなななんと盛りだくさんでございます！
Whoa! This time, too, it's packed with so many things!
今回イラストは、D福先生に描いていただきました！ ありがとうございます！
The illustrations this time were drawn by D-Fuku-sensei! Thank you very much!
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう！ まずは、こちら！
Now let's look at the details! First, this!
ダダダ！ 抱き枕カバー！
Dadada! Dakimakura cover!
ということで、今回のゆるふわな、私服の衣装で寝転がっているAZKiの抱き枕カバーが出ます！
So, a dakimakura cover featuring AZKi lying down in this soft and fluffy casual outfit is coming out!
うわー！ まさかグッズになるとは思いもよりませんでしたが、ぜひチェックしてください！ 続いては、こちら！
Whoa! I never thought it would become merchandise, but please check it out! Next up is this!
缶バッジセット！
Can badge set!
こちらね、ハートの形をした缶バッジとなっております。
These are heart-shaped can badges.
キラキラのホログラム仕様となっておりますので、いっぱい、いっぱい、つけてほしいなと思います！ 続いては、こちら！
They have a sparkly hologram finish, so I hope you'll pin them on lots of things! Next up is this!
開拓者ぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Pioneer plushie key holder!
ということで、ホロライブフレンズwithuのAZKiと、大体、あの、同じぐらいのね、ちっちゃいサイズになってますんで、
So, it's about the same small size as the Hololive Friends with u AZKi plushie,
一緒に、あの、持ち歩いてもらえるようなサイズ感となっておりますので、
making it a perfect size to carry around with you.
一緒にね、あずぬいと、開拓者ぬいで、お出かけしてほしいなと思います！ 続いては、こちら！
I hope you'll take Azu-nui and Pioneer-nui out with you together! Next up is this!
開拓者アイマスク！
Pioneer eye mask!
ま、今回抱き枕カバーと一緒に、もうね、安眠できるね、グッズをね、ご用意いたしましたので、こちらもぜひ、寝る時に使ってほしいなと思います！ そして、続いては、こちら！
Well, with the dakimakura cover, we've prepared goods for a good night's sleep, so I hope you'll use this when you sleep! Next up is this!
ボイス！ ASMRボイス！
Voice! ASMR voice!
ボイスタイトルは、『AZKiのわがままをきいて』というね、
The voice title is "Listen to AZKi's Selfishness,"
ちょっとAZKiが、ちょっとしたわがままを言って、君をね、デートに誘うシチュエーションとなっておりますので、
a situation where AZKi says some slightly selfish things and invites you on a date.
今回のね、この、ゆるふわ私服衣装のAZKiを思い浮かべて聞いてください！
Please listen while imagining AZKi in this soft and fluffy casual outfit!
そして、フルセット購入特典もございます！ こちら！
And there's also a bonus for purchasing the full set! Here!
なんと、数量限定は、AZKiの直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと、特典ASMRボイス！
The limited quantity version includes a bromide card with AZKi's hand-written signature, and a bonus ASMR voice!
タイトルは、『寝起きのAZKiと』ということで、
The title is "With AZKi Just Waking Up,"
こちらね、抱き枕カバーのね、なんか、ちょっと裏面のイラストをイメージしたシチュエーションとなっておりますので、こちらも一緒に楽しんでいただけたらなと思います！
which is a situation inspired by the illustration on the back of the dakimakura cover, so I hope you enjoy this too!
そしてですね、数量限定がなくなり次第、箔押しの複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと、特典ASMRボイス、同様の『寝起きのAZKiと』となっておりますので、よろしくお願いします。
And after the limited quantity ones are gone, it will be a bromide card with a replica signature and the same ASMR voice bonus. Thank you.
改めて、フルセットは、こちらとなります！ じゃん！
Once again, here's the full set! Ta-da!
いやー、いっぱいね、ありますね。買うならね、やっぱりね、フルセットが、いいですよ。みんな、よろしくね、この後。
Wow, there are so many things. If you're going to buy, the full set is definitely the way to go. Everyone, thank you in advance.
はい、そして、さらに、タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典といたしまして、
Yes, and furthermore, as a full set bonus for the Talent Premium Goods...
去年から発売された、hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEで使用できるカードが1枚つきます！
one card usable in the Hololive Official Card Game, released last year, will be included!
カードは、hololive production OFFICIAL SHOPで購入された方のみ対象となります。
The card is only for those who purchase from the Hololive Production official shop.
特典につくのは、推しをアピールできる、キーカード、推しホロメンカードでございます。
The bonus is a key card, an 'Oshi Holomen Card', which lets you show off your favorite.
カードの詳細や、遊び方については、ホームページをご確認ください。
Please check the website for card details and how to play.
同梱されるカードは、日本語版のみとなります。
The included card will be the Japanese version only.
ございますので、ご了承ください。
...so please be aware of that.
以上、AZKi誕生日記念2025のグッズ情報でした！
That's all for the AZKi Birthday Celebration 2025 goods information!
みんな買ってね、是非。よろしくお願いします！
Please buy them, everyone. I'm counting on you!
ということで、お待たせいたしました。
And now, thank you for waiting.
さらに重大発表ございます！
We have a major announcement!
それではお待たせいたしました。こちらをご覧ください。
Well then, thank you for waiting. Please take a look at this.
重大発表
Major Announcement
はい、ということで、AZKiの新しいEP『Restart』と『Rebirth』が...
Yes! So, AZKi's new EPs "Restart" and "Rebirth"...
...11月5日にリリースすることが決定しましたー！
...are set to be released on November 5th!
今回は初めてとなる2作同時リリースとなっております。
This will be the first-ever simultaneous release of two works.
このあと21時より、ホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップと...
Reservations start at 21:00 today at the Hololive Production Official Shop and...
...全国のCDショップで予約が開始されます。
...CD shops nationwide.
そして1枚目の『Restart』には...
And the first one, "Restart,"...
...AZKiの新しい魅力が詰まった新曲4曲。
...features four new songs filled with AZKi's new charm.
2枚目の『Rebirth』には、イノナカミュージック時代の楽曲4曲の...
The second one, "Rebirth," contains rearranged versions of four songs...
...リアレンジバージョンが収録されます。
...from the INoNaKa Music era.
そして、CD限定特典として、それぞれボーナストラックに...
Also, as a CD-exclusive bonus, a version of "The Last Frontier"...
...すいちゃんと歌った『The Last Frontier』が1種類ずつ収録されます。
...sung with Sui-chan will be included in each as a bonus track.
また、通常盤には限定特典として...
Additionally, the standard edition comes with...
...ランダムアナザージャケットが1枚付いてきます。
...one random another jacket as a limited bonus.
なんとこちらには、数量限定で私の...
And apparently, some of these might even include...
...直筆サイン入りが入っているかも？とのことです。
...my hand-written signature in limited quantities!
各種CDショップでの購入特典はこちらです！
Here are the purchase bonuses from various CD shops!
特典の絵柄は後日発表します。
The bonus designs will be announced at a later date.
さらに、ホロライブオフィシャルショップでは...
Furthermore, a complete set will be available...
...セットになったコンプリート盤を発売します！
...at the Hololive Official Shop!
コンプリート盤にはここでしか手に入らないたくさんの特典も付いております。
The complete set comes with many bonuses that can only be obtained here.
数にこちら限りがございますので、お早めに！
Quantities are limited, so please be quick!
そして1点、ホロライブオフィシャルショップのアルバム購入について注意事項がございます。
And one point, there are some precautions regarding album purchases at the Hololive Official Shop.
完全生産限定コンプリート盤は発売日での提供となりますので...
The Made-to-Order Complete Edition will be delivered on the release date...
...EP以外のグッズとの商品は同時購入できません。
...so it cannot be purchased together with goods other than the EP.
通常盤は他のグッズとの同時購入が可能ですが...
The standard edition can be purchased with other goods...
...店頭販売日以降のお届けになる可能性があるので、こちらご注意ください。
...but note it might be delivered after the store release date, so please be careful.
詳しくは販売サイトの注意事項をご確認ください。
Please check the precautions on the sales site for more details.
はい！そして最後にもう一つお知らせあります。
Yes! And one last announcement.
今回発表したこのニューEP『Restart』の中から...
From the new EP "Restart" announced today...
...『未来カンパネラ』という楽曲を本日24時にデジタルリリースします！
...the song "Mirai Campanella" will be released digitally today at midnight!
配信終了後にはミュージックビデオもプレミア公開しちゃいますということで...
After the stream, the music video will also have a premiere...
...ぜひチェックしてください！
...so please check it out!
うわー！いっぱい情報がありましたが、みんなついてこれましたか？
Whoa! That was a lot of information, did everyone keep up?
はい。ということで、ライブも次の曲で最後になります。
Yes. So, the live performance is also coming to the last song.
最後はね、AZKiの新しい曲を聴いていただきたいと思います。
For the finale, I'd like you to listen to AZKi's new song.
それでは聴いてください、『未来カンパネラ』。
Please listen to it: "Mirai Campanella."
もっと もっと
More, more
鏡よ教えて 私の証は
Mirror, please tell me, where is the proof
どこにあるのだろう 分からない 分からないよ
of my existence? I don't know, I just don't know.
周りと比べたって 虚しくなるだけ
Even if I compare myself to others, it only makes me feel empty.
あぁノイズが 海鳴りのようにナミダを奪う
Ah, the noise steals my tears like the roaring of the sea.
切り取った風景を 道しるべにしよう
Let's make the captured scenery our guide.
そら、傷ついた感情も
The sky, and even these wounded emotions...
連れて行くから
Because I'll take you with me
そっと響くカンパネラ
The Campanella softly ringing
新しい未来を感じてる
I'm feeling a new future
怖くたって進むしかないでしょ
Even if I'm scared, I have to keep going, right?
遠くまで
To the ends of the earth
届けこの祈りよ 光となれ
Reach out, my prayer, and become light
もっと もっと
More and more
少しずつでもいい「私」という答えを
Even if it's little by little, give me the answer called 'me'
もっと
More
もっと…
More...
夜空よ教えて
Night sky, please tell me
私の証は
Whether the proof of my existence
輝けるのかな
Can shine
見つけたい 見つけたいよ
I want to find it, I want to find it
誰かの決めたレールは
The rails determined by someone else
苦しくなるだけ
Only make me suffer
ねぇ ノイズも力に変えるよ
Hey, I'll turn even the noise into strength
ココロに誓う
I swear it to my heart
錆びついた運命の歯車を回そう
Let's turn the rusted gears of fate
ほら 着飾った感情は
Look, these dressed-up emotions
脱ぎ捨てるから
I'm casting them off
そっと紡ぐシンフォニア
The symphonia I softly weave
叶えたい願いを信じてる
I believe in the wish I want to come true
胸を張って歌うしかないでしょ
I have to puff out my chest and sing, right?
全力で
With all my might
やがて希望の歌に変わる日まで
Until the day it finally turns into a song of hope
もっと もっと
More and more
悩みながらでいい すべてが宝物
It's okay to worry, everything is a treasure
いつの日かこの声を 受け取ってくれたなら
If one day you receive this voice of mine
この言葉を君に
I'll give these words to you
「もう大丈夫 一人じゃない」
'It's okay now, you're not alone'
強い想いを繋ぐよ
I'll connect these strong feelings
一歩踏み出してみた 優しく世界は微笑む
I took a step forward, and the world smiled kindly
高鳴る気持ちに身を任せて
Entrusting myself to these racing feelings
さあ行こう
Let's go
そっと響くカンパネラ
The Campanella softly ringing
新しい未来を感じてる
I'm feeling a new future
怖くたって進むしかないでしょ
Even if I'm scared, I have to keep going, right?
遠くまで
To the ends of the earth
届けこの祈りよ 光となれ
Reach out, my prayer, and become light
もっと もっと
More and more
少しずつでもいい「私」という答えを
Even if it's little by little, give me the answer called 'me'
もっと
More
もっと…
More...
ごめん、待った？
Sorry, did I keep you waiting?
ごめんね、ライブ終わった後マネージャーさんに呼ばれちゃって
Sorry, I was called by my manager after the concert ended.
もちろん打ち上げもあったけど、君と会うためにキャンセルしたんだからね
Of course, there was an after-party, but I canceled it just to meet you.
改めて、今日はライブに来てくれてありがとう
Once again, thank you for coming to the concert today.
アリーナ席の右の方にいたよね？
You were on the right side of the arena seats, weren't you?
ちゃんと見つけたよ
I spotted you clearly.
実は、今日花火大会なんだって
Actually, I heard there's a fireworks festival today.
こんな都会で花火あがるの、ロマンチックだなぁ
Fireworks going off in a city like this, it's so romantic, isn't it?
ねぇ、見て見て！今日のライブのキービジュアルだよ
Hey, look, look! It's the key visual for today's concert.
もしかしたら、ここでも流れてたのかな？
Maybe it was playing here too?
ついさっきのことだから、ちょっと恥ずかしいよ
Since it was just a moment ago, it's a bit embarrassing.
でも、とっても楽しかったなぁ
But it was so much fun.
あ、雨？
Ah, rain?
どうしよう、私、傘持ってないよ
What should I do? I don't have an umbrella.
あ、傘持ってきてくれたんだ
Ah, you brought an umbrella for me.
ありがとう、かっこいいじゃん
Thank you. That's pretty cool of you.
でも、傘一つしかないってことは、これって…
But, the fact that there's only one umbrella means, this is...
相合傘だよね？
Sharing an umbrella, right?
私、相合傘って初めてで、これってさ…
It's my first time sharing an umbrella like this, and you know, this is...
はい、ドキドキするね
Yes, it's exciting, isn't it?
あ、雨が止んだ
Oh, the rain has stopped.
通り雨だったのかな？
Was it a passing shower?
なんか、雨止んで嬉しいような、悲しいような...
Somehow, I'm both happy and sad the rain stopped...
もっと、君と相合傘したかったな
I wanted to share an umbrella with you a bit longer.
なんてね
Just kidding.
雨も止んだし、
The rain has stopped,
雨で人通りも少なくなったし、さ、グリコゲームでもしようよ
and there are fewer people around because of it. So, let's play the Glico game.
ここからスタートね
Starting from here, okay?
いくよ、じゃんけんぽん！
Here we go, rock-paper-scissors!
やったー、私の勝ち！
Yay, I won!
ち、い、よ、こ、れ、い、と！
Chi-yo-ko-re-i-to!
ちょっと何？ニヤニヤして見てるの？
Wait, what? Why are you watching me with that grin?
え？可愛いって？
Eh? You say I'm cute?
もう、ちょっと恥ずかしいからやめてよ
Geez, stop it, it's a bit embarrassing.
次いくよ、じゃんけんぽん！
Next round, rock-paper-scissors!
グ、リ、コ！
Gu-ri-ko!
だから、ちょっとニヤニヤやめてってば
I said, stop that grinning.
次いくよ、じゃんけんぽん！
Next round, rock-paper-scissors!
ぱ、い、な、つ、ぷ、る！
Pa-i-na-tsu-pu-ru!
もうじゃんけん弱すぎだよ
Gosh, you're way too weak at rock-paper-scissors.
絶対わざと負けてるでしょ？
You're definitely losing on purpose, aren't you?
もういい加減にしてよね
Oh, give me a break.
え？なに？こっち来てって？
Eh? What? You want me to come here?
どこいくの？
Where are we going?
なに、なに？見せたいものがある？
What is it, what is it? You have something you want to show me?
あのモニターを見ろって？
You want me to look at that monitor?
3, 2, 1...
え、え、どういうこと？お誕生日おめでとう！？
Eh, eh, what does this mean? "Happy Birthday"!?
この1年がAZKiにとって楽しくて素敵な日々になりますように
May this year be full of fun and wonderful days for AZKi.
えー、ありがとう！サプライズしてくれたんだ！
Eh-, thank you! You gave me a surprise!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
いつも一番近くで応援してくれて本当にありがとう
Thank you so much for always supporting me from the closest possible distance.
これからもろしくね
I look forward to our time together from now on as well.
きれい...
So beautiful...
素敵な誕生日にしてくれてありがとう
Thank you for making this such a wonderful birthday.
お礼にこのあと君だけのアンコールライブ、するね
As a thank you, I'll perform an encore live just for you after this.
これからもずっと一緒にいてね
Please stay with me forever.
今日も誕生日お祝いしてくれてありがとう！新衣装のAZKiもよろしくね！！ だいすき
Thank you for celebrating my birthday again today! Please treat the new-costume AZKi well too!! I love you.
【3D LIVE】AZKi 7th Birthday Live "Sweet Pop Story"
新衣装お披露目＆重大発表あり #AZKi生誕ライブ2025
[3D LIVE] AZKi 7th Birthday Live "Sweet Pop Story"
New Outfit Reveal & Major Announcement #AZKiBirthdayLive2025